So I click on upload photo again and as you see this time I have something
pretty different so I open this one up to see how this one is going. Yes so as
I see it likes my photo and by clicking on generate, confirm your headshot
styles, yep, I like them and by clicking on generate all, we'll be able to wait until
we see what we get. So it's going to take us some time and as you see it says
get your headshots with 20% off, upgrade, I don't want to do that for now so
I close this and I click generate again. Okay so I think it's not doable with
the very plan that we're using and we need to upgrade and we need to pay it.
So I come back, yes it is written free over here so I come back and choose all
the free options this time. I just want to see what I get at the end. So I
uncheck all of these premium options and I choose from these free these three
free ones and also this summer looks you know so now we have four but they're
all free. I click upload photo again and I choose my avatar